Guide to the John Ewart Wallace Sterling, Chancellor of Stanford University, Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Series 1
  - Stanford University
    - Hoover Presidential Library Association News Volume II- No. 5, 1974 May (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Hoover Presidential Library Association News Volume I- No. 4, 1973 July (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Hoover Presidential Library Association News Volume I- No. 4, 1973 Aug. (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Hoover Presidential Library Association News Volume I - No. 10, 1973 Dec. (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Hoover Presidential Library Association News Volume 1 - No. 9, 1973 Nov. (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Hoover Presidential Library Association News Volume I - No. 8, 1973 Oct. (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Hoover Presidential Libray Association News Volum I - No. 3, 1973 May (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - The Library Dedication Programs (Detailed), 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Preliminary Report Funding Prospects: Germany and Italy, 1969 Aug. 19 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - International Studies Presidential Advisory Committee First Meeting, 1969 Nov. 6-7 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - International Studies Presidential Advisory Committee Second Meeting, 1968 Sept. 19-20 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Annual Report: The 1967 Ford Foundation for International Studies 1970-1971, 1971 Sept. (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Technical Assiatnce in the Seventies: The Role of the University and of Stanford in Particular, 1971 April 15-16 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Meeting of the President's Visiting Committee, 1971 April 15-16 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Letter from Spaeth to Wallace Sterling, 1971 April (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Draft of Report to President richard W. Lyman by President's Visiting Commitee on International Studies, 1971 April (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Annual Report: The 1967 and 1972 Ford Foundation Grants for International Studies 1972-1973, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Annual report: The 1967 and 1972 Ford Foundations Grants for International Studies, 1973 Nov. (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Various Letter to and From Sterling 1968-1972 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Annual Report: The 1967 Ford Foundation Grant for International Studies 1971-1972, 1972 Oct. (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Annual Report: The 1967 Ford Foundation Grant for International Studies 1971-1972, 1972 Oct. (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Robert Ward Letters, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Report on Higher Education, 1971 March (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Board of Education and Milton Marks Letters/ ACSUS Newsletter, 1971-1975 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Seminar 191: The Making of Decisions, 1971 Winter (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Freshman Seminar - Making of Decisions, 1970-1971 Winter (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Senior Colloquia, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - International Studies, 1969-1975 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1962 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1961 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1960 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1959 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1958 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1957 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1949 April.-1950 Jan. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Week at a Glance Booklet, 1949 Jan.-June (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Week at a Glance Booklet, 1948 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Little Blue Calendar Booklet, 1974 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Little Blue Calendar Booklet, 1973 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1963 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1963 Dec.-1964 Dec. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1965 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1966 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1967 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1969 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1970 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1971 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1972 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1973 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1973 Dec.-1974 Dec. (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1977 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1978 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1979 Jan.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1979 Dec.-1980 Dec. (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1980 Dec.-1981 Dec. (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1981 Dec.-1982 Dec. (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1982 Dec,-1983 Dec. (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Weekly Appointments Book, 1984 Dec.-1985 Dec. (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - United Grants Committee Annual Survey, 1962-1963, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - United Grants Committee Annual Survey, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - United Grants Committee Annual Survey, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - United Grants Committee Annual Survey, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Exchequer Grant, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1959-1960 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Exchequer Grant, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Exchequer Grant, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1958-1958 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1957-158 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1954-1955 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1953-1954 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1951-1952 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1950-1951 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1949-1950 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Box of Teaching and Research Notes, 1940-1945 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1952-1953 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1947-1948 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1945-1946 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1944-1945 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1943-1944 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1942-1943 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1941-1942 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Handwritten Notes and University Grants Committee: Returns from Universities and University Colleges in Receipt of Treasury Grant, 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Wallace Sherling Box of Notes, 1914 June-Aug. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - I9, 1973-1983 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - J10, 1972-1983 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - K11, 1969-1982 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - L12, 1972-1984 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - M13, 1972-1983 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - N15, 1974-1981 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - O16, 1970-1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - P17, 1973-1984 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Q18, 1977-1982 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - R19, 1976-1984 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - S20, 1970-1983 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - T21, 1968-1983 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - U22, 1978-1981 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - V23, 1974-1982 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - W24, 1969-1983 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - XYZ25, 1974-1983 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Salutations and Signatures - Campaign Mailing, 1972 Aug (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Campaign, 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Events - Merril Corporate Lunch, 1972 Sep 13 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Robert L Conway, 1972 Dec 12 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Corporate Gifts General, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Foundation Gifts General, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Major Gifts Plan, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Special Gifts, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Trustees, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Organization, 1972 Feb 2 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Volunteer Group, 1972-1976 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Major Gifts Committee Arizona, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Major Gifts Committee Los Angeles Area, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Major Gifts Committee Northern California Area, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Major Gifts committee Northern Texas, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Major Gifts Committee New York Area, 1972-1976 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Major Gifts Committee Ohio, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Volunteer Leadership Seminars, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Case Statement, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Newsletters, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Publicity, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Speeches (miscellaneous), Undated (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Stanford Talking Points, 1972 July (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - The Campaign for Stanford Premlimanry Planning, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Background to Current Studies, 1970 Mar 4 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - PACE Case Statement, Undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - PACE Backgorund and Reference, 1970 Mar 4 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Trustees Meetings, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Trustees, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Governor's Corner Dedication, 1983 Oct. 27 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Alexander Von Humbolt Foundation, 1983 Aug. 29 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Carl Franklin, 1983 April 19 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Gene Farber, 1982 Nov. 12 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Richard Guggenhime, 1982 Nov. 9 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - John W. Gardner, 1982 Sept. 13 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Green Library Mortgage Burning, 1982 June 14 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Thomas S. barclay, 1982 Jan. 31 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - The Thacher School, 1981 Nov. 13 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Sterling Quadrangle Gound-Breaking, 1981 Oct. 12 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Stanford Guide Service, 1981 May 20 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Peter Bing, 1981 May 11 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Fred H. Merrill, 1981 Jan. 15 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Donald Kennedy Iauguration and Investiture, 1980 Oct. 12 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Bill Lowe Returement Party, 1980 July 1 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Margaret Jacks Hall Dedication, 1980 June 20 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Commencement, 1980 June 15 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Wallace Award, 1980 May 6 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Scientific Symposium Medical School, 1980 March 27 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Library Associates, 1980 Feb. 22 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Medical School Celebration, 1980 Feb. 11 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - History Corner Deidcation, 1980 Feb. 8 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Arjay Miller, 1979 May 14 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Sunset Club, 1979 April 23 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Fred Terman Uncommon Man, 1978 Dec. 7 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Richard E. Guggenhime, 1978 Sept. 11 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Frank F. Walker Memorial, 1978 Aug. 1 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Katherine Branson School, 1978 May 31 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Polytechnic School, 1978 April 20 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Uncommon Man, 1978 March 10 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Ernest W. McFarland, 1977 Dec. 4 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Lord Ashby, 1977 Oct. 9 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Law Alumni Dinner, 1977 Oct. 7 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Fred Glover & Ken Cuthbertson, 1977 April 11 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Castilleja Cornerstone Deidication Catilleja School, PA, 1976 June 7 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Luncheon Houston, Texas, 1976 April 30 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Dinner Honoring David Hamburg, MD Faculty Club, 1976 May 24 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Party for Bob and Louise Walker Faculty Club, 1976 Apr 22 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Volunteer Meeting New York, 1976 Mar 25 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Stanford Faculty Women's Club "Reminiscences", 1976 Jan 12 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Graduate School of Business Fiftieth Anniversary, 1975 Oct 25 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - GSB -- Fiftieth Anniversary, 1975 Oct 25 (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - David Harris Memorial Memorial Church, 1975 Sept 3 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Santa Barbara Dinner PR Bush, host, 1975 Feb 11 (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Uncommon Man Award Luncheon for May Goodan, 1975 Feb 10 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Leadership Conference Dinner Gold Spike Awards, 1974 Nov 8 (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Luncheon for John Clarkin Stanford Faculty Club, 1974 Oct 31 (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - 25th Anniversary Reminiscences Faculty Club Party, 1974 Apr 15 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Blake Wilbur Memorial Service Memorial Church, 1974 Mar 18 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Founders' Day Reception Hotel Mark Hopkins, 1974 Mar 11 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Kaiser Dinner, 1974 Feb 17 (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Dinner for Bob Spears Faculty Club, 1974 Jan 18 (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Leadership Conference Dinner (Gold Spike Awards), 1973 Oct 12 (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - The Morning Forum of Los Altos, 1973 Dec 4 (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - Campaign Volunteers Seminar Campus, 1973 Mar 18-20 (Box 35, Folder 55)
    - Annual Fund -- Cocktail Party Houston, Texas, 1973 Jan 24 (Box 35, Folder 56)
    - British Higher Education: A Porpourri Looking for a Pot Sunset Club Dinner, 1973 Jan 31 (Box 35, Folder 57)
    - Campaign Volunteers Seminar Campus, 1972 Nov 19-21 (Box 35, Folder 58)
    - Law Alumni Assembly Campus, 1972 Oct 6 (Box 35, Folder 59)
    - Leadership Conference and Dinner Campus, 1972 Oct 5-7 (Box 35, Folder 60)
    - Alumni Exuective Board Bowman House, 1972 May 19 (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - New York Alumni, 1972 Mar 15 (Box 35, Folder 62)
    - Stanford Research Institute Dinner, 1972 Mar 9 (Box 35, Folder 63)
    - Founders Day Program Memorial Church, 1972 Mar 5 (Box 35, Folder 64)
    - Loyola/Marymount Dinner Los Angeles, 1972 Feb 11 (Box 35, Folder 65)
    - Dinner for Pettits Faculty Club, 1972 Feb 5 (Box 35, Folder 66)
    - John Azra McDowell Portrait Unveiling at Bowman House, 1972 Jan 3 (Box 35, Folder 67)
    - Law School Dinner Rickey's, 1971 Nov 19 (Box 35, Folder 68)
    - Leadership Conference Awards Dinner, 1971 Sept 24 (Box 35, Folder 69)
    - Dedication/Emilie Dohrmann Grove, 1971 Sept 24 (Box 35, Folder 70)
    - Rendcomb Oxford, England, 1971 Jun 26 (Box 35, Folder 71)
    - Rotary Club of Reno Reno, Nevada, 1971 May 17 (Box 35, Folder 72)
    - Casteilleja Dinner for Miss Espinosa Menlo Country Club, 1971 May 5 (Box 35, Folder 73)
    - National Brotherhood Award Dinner (Ben Swig) Fairmont Hotel, 1971 Apr 28 (Box 35, Folder 74)
    - Dinner for Alf Brandin Stanford Faculty Club, 1971 Apr 12 (Box 35, Folder 75)
    - Tulane University Luncheon New Orleans, LA, 1971 Apr 1 (Box 35, Folder 76)
    - Dinner Honoring Pres. and Mrs Lyman Maples Pavilion, 1971 Mar 9 (Box 35, Folder 77)
    - Ruth Wattis Mitchell Building Dedication Ceremony, 1970 Nov 19 (Box 35, Folder 78)
    - University of Alberta Convocation Edmonton, Alberta, Canada, 1970 Oct 31 (Box 35, Folder 79)
    - Dinner for Roger Heynes Bohemian Club, 1970 Oct 21 (Box 35, Folder 80)
    - Bissinger Center for Radiation Therapy - Dedication, 1970 Sept 12 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Stanford-Sloan Graduation Dinner - P.A. Hills Golf and Country Club, 1970 June 4 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Law Society of Southern California - Los Angeles, 1970 May 15 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Fund American Companies / Shaw and Begg - Toronto Dinner, 1970 March 25 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Founders Day Service, 1970 March 8 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Dinner Honoring Willi Strothmann - Faculty Club, 1970 March 5 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Dinner for David S. Jacobson - Stanford Faculty Club, 1970 Jan 12 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Peninsula Harvard Club - Golden Pavilion/Los Altos, 1969 Oct 29 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - English-Speaking Union - National Council/Los Angeles, 1969 Oct 27 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Ira Lillick Portrait Unveiling - Stanford Faculty Club, 1969 Oct 18 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Gold Spike Awards - Leadership Conference Dinner, 1969 Sept 26 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Dedication of Roscoe Maples Pavilion, 1969 Mar 1 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Students Unrest - Shell Centre, London, 1969 April 16 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Stanford Club of London - London, England, 1968 Dec 4 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Report to Board of Trustees, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - International Congress of Applied Mechanics - campus, 1968 Aug 23 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Commencement 1968 (Last Major Address by Dr. Sterling while President of Stanford), 1968 June 16 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Class Day Activities, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Changes and Chances - Commencement - University of Utah, 1968 June 7 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Dinner Honoring Ernest C. Arbuckle, 1968 June 6 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Emeritus Professor Tom Bailey, 1968 May (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Inauguration of Charles J. Hitch - President, Univ. of California, 1968 May 23 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Alumni Association Dinner Party to honor Dr. and Mrs. Sterling, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Alumni Clubs and Conferences, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Gun Club Dinner - the Family, 1968 May 2 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Memorial Service for Ralph Haswell Lutz, 1968 April 17 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Dinner for President Hitch, 1968 April 10 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Council for Financial aid to Education, 1968 Feb 27 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Dinner, 1968 Jan 31 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1968 Jan 16 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Taft Institute of Government, 1968 Jan 13 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Greetings to Visiting Com. School fo Education, 1968 Jan 5 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Report to Board of Trustees, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - William F. Herrin Hall & Wm. F. Herrin Laboratories Dedication, 1964 Nov 30 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Charter Day - Columbia University, 1967 Oct 31 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Parents Luncheon - New York, 1967 Oct 26 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Inauguration of Robert J. Wert, as Pres. of Mills College, 1967 Oct 18 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Graduate School of Business - Faculty Meeting, 1967 Oct 11 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Lou Henry Hoover Building Dedication Milbank and de Basily Rooms, 1967 October 9 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Parents Day, 1967 October 7 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Report of the President - Annual Owners Mtg. Palo Alto - Stanford Hospital Center, 1967 Oct 4 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Dean of Students Dinner (RA's, etc.), 1967 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Freshman Convocation, 1967 Sept 20 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Leadership Conference - campus, 1967 Sept 16 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Women's Clubhouse Gift Acceptance Ceremony, 1967 Sept 13 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center Dedication, 1967 Sept 9 (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - The turning of the Leaves - the Family Farm, 1967 Aug 31 (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Class Day Activities, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Alumni Clubs and Conferences, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Harry F Camp Memorial Lectures by Dr. King-man Brewster (Sterling introductory remarks for Dr. Kingman Brewster), 1967 May 7 (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - Law Society of Northern California and Nevada Dinner Honoring Emeriti Professors, 1967 April 28 (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Extent of Responsibilities in Student Life - Association of American Universities, 1967 April 24-May (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - The Stanford Alumni Association Presentation of Hoover Medal to the Hon. Carl Hayden, 1967 April 24 (Box 36, Folder 53)
    - Memorial Service for Victor C. Twitty, 1967 April 12 (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - Introduction fo Nikolay Fedorenko - Russion Ambassador to UN, 1967 March 7 (Box 36, Folder 55)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1967 Jan 24 (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - Mothers' Club, 1967 Jan 17 (Box 36, Folder 57)
    - Bechtel International Student Center Dedicated, 1967 Jan 13 (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - The Asia Foundation Conference on University Cooperation and Asian Development - Hong Kong, 1966 Dec 18-21 (Box 36, Folder 59)
    - John Stauffer Laboratory for Chemical Engineering (Stauffer III) Dedication, 1966 Dec 12 (Box 36, Folder 60)
    - Dedication of Undergraduate Library, 1966 Dec 2 (Box 36, Folder 61)
    - Stanford Associates Dinner - Los Angeles, 1966 Nov 30 (Box 36, Folder 62)
    - Graduate School of Business Dedication - Dr. Sterling's Remarks, 1966 Oct 7 (Box 36, Folder 63)
    - Roble Hall, 1966 Sept 29 (Box 36, Folder 64)
    - Graduate Convocation, 1966 Sept 25 (Box 36, Folder 65)
    - Transfer Assembly, 1966 Sept 24 (Box 36, Folder 66)
    - Dean of Students Dinner (RA's, etc.), 1966 Sept 23 (Box 36, Folder 67)
    - AGPS Conference (Leadership Conference), 1966 Sept 23 (Box 36, Folder 68)
    - Freshman Convocation, 1966 Sept 21 (Box 36, Folder 69)
    - Commencement, 1966 June 12 (Box 36, Folder 70)
    - International Center for the Advancement of Management Education, 1966 June 3 (Box 36, Folder 71)
    - McMaster University Convocation, 1966 May 30 (Box 36, Folder 72)
    - Clinical Sciences Research Building Dedication, 1966 May 26 (Box 36, Folder 73)
    - ROTC Review, 1966 May 24 (Box 36, Folder 74)